(Amy:)I know you're not ready,
(Amy:)and I don't want you to say it
(Leonard:)just because
social convention dictates...
(Sheldon:)I love you, too.
(Amy:)You said it.
(Sheldon:)There's no denying
I have feelings for you
(Sheldon:)that can't be explained
in any other way.
(Sheldon:)I briefly considered
that I had a brain parasite.
(Sheldon:)But that seems even
more farfetched.
(Sheldon:)The only conclusion was love.
(Sheldon:)I know what's happening.
(Sheldon:)This is a panic attack.
(Sheldon:)SoccerMom09 says to lie down
with your feet elevated.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Stuart:)Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
(Sheldon:)Just because I love you
doesn't mean
(Sheldon:)girls are allowed in my room.